{
	"decks": [
		{
			"name": "Harmony",
			"description": "New learnings from Harmony book",
			"tags": ["music theory", "composition"],
			"cards": [
				{
					"question": "What tones are in a triad",
					"answer": "Tonic, mediant, dominant"
				},
				{
					"question": "Who is Chopin",
					"answer": "Solo pianist"
				},
				{
					"question": "What is your favorite color",
					"answer": "Green"
				}
			],
			"favs": 1
		},
		{
			"name": "AWS_Certified_Developer",
			"description": "Review material from Udemy",
			"tags": ["AWS", "cloud"],
			"cards": [
				{
					"question": "What is the EC2 service",
					"answer": "Elastic Compute Cloud"
				},
				{
					"question": "Where is the Route53 name derived from",
					"answer": "Route66 was first USA route and 53 is DNS port for publicly exposing to internet"
				},
				{
					"question": "What is Amazon's data warehousing service",
					"answer": "RedShift"
				},
				{
					"question": "How many AWS regions are there (2017)",
					"answer": "14"
				},
				{
					"question": "What is IAM responsible for",
					"answer": "Create and give users permissions"
				},
				{
					"question": "What is the root AWS account",
					"answer": "The AWS email used to sign up for AWS"
				},
				{
					"question": "What are some steps afte setting up an account",
					"answer": "Change link for users to sign on.  Multifactor auth.  Create users.  Associate to groups."
				},
				{
					"question": "What default permissions do new AWS users have after created",
					"answer": "None, they must be added to groups or have policies attached manually"
				},
				{
					"question": "What is an IAM group and why is it useful",
					"answer": "Groups are definable sets of policies.  Users assigned to a group get all policies assigned to that group.  It is much easier to add a user to a group than to add many policies individually to each user."
				},
				{
					"question": "What is an IAM policy",
					"answer": "Define actions, services, and more that a user has access to within AWS"
				}
			],
			"favs": 4
		},
		{
			"name": "Audio_Recording",
			"description": "Pro Tools and audio recording techniques.",
			"tags": ["recording", "pro tools", "audio"],
			"cards": [
				{
					"question": "",
					"answer": ""
				},
				{
					"question": "What options are available fo rgrouped PT audio",
					"answer": "Mix, edit, and mix/edit"
				},
				{
					"question": "What is voice priority",
					"answer": "When > 32 tracks of audio, voice priority determines which 32 are heard.  The first 32 in the list are heard."
				}
			],
			"favs": 0
		}
	]
}